( phone rings )
( hoarsely ):
Hello?
( coughs )
( hoarsely ):
Hello?
I love my new job!
Honey, you're screaming.
You bet your ass I am!
I just had the best
first day ever.
The kitchen? Twice as big
as Allesandro's.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah, and clean?
Not just
Health Department clean
Monica clean!
Awesome.
Oh, and the people are so nice.
There's this one guy, Jeffrey--
he's the maitre d'.
Chandler, you will love him.
He is without a doubt the
funniest guy I have ever met.
Captioning sponsored by
NBC
and WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
This is nice.
I know.
You need both hands
for that?
Yeah, I kind of do.
Well, how's this?
Yeah?
Well, look at you two,
holding hands.
Huh? Is this getting serious?
( both stammering )
Have you not talked
about it yet?
Am I making you uncomfortable?!
If you were bigger,
you'd hit me, huh?
Ah!
I'm sorry.
So sorry. It's obviously
way too early
for us to be having
that conversation.
Is it?
Maybe not. Is it?
Okay
when I got divorced,
I-I didn't think
I'd feel this way
about someone for
a really long time.
Mm-hmm.
Then again, I didn't think
I'd meet someone like you
and... this may
be crazy soon
but I want you to have this.
No, not... that's gum.
Oh, five bucks.
I love it when that happens,
you know?
It's like you don't know
it's there...
I know, Mike.
Why don't you keep digging?
Oh, sorry.
Oh, it's a key.
To be honest, I think
I'd prefer the five dollars.
It's to my apartment.
Oh, wow. Ooh.
Big step for Phoebe and Mike.
Yeah, look, and I don't want
you to feel like
you have to give me your key
just because...
Oh, no, I want to.
Oh, thank God.
Yeah. Ooh. Wow.
I was starting to think
that I'd never meet someone
that, you know, I wanted to...
do this with.
Here you go.
This is cool, huh?
It really is.
Oh, I know it.
It is amazing.
These little things
open doors.
So, I don't go back to work
for another four weeks
but we would like our nanny
to start right away
so that Emma could get a chance
to know her.
I think that's really smart.
The easier we can make
the transition
for her, the better.
That's great! Great.
So do you have
any questions for us?
Not really.
All right.
Well, thank you so much
for coming.
Thank you.
Really nice
to meet you
and we will call you.
Oh, you know, wait.
I do have one question.
Do you guys do
random drug testing?
Boy, we, uh...
hadn't really thought
of that.
That's cool.
But if you do
I'm gonna need
three days notice.
Okeydokey!
Wow. We're never going
to find a nanny.
Oh, come on, Rach.
We will. I promise.
We have more interviews.
Oh...
And, worse comes to worst
we can always reconsider
the first one we met with.
What, the blond
with no bra?!
She was blond?
( knocking on door )
Just a sec!
Okay, okay.
This one's name is Sandy.
Okay.
She's got a degree
in Early Childhood Education.
Uh, she worked for
her last family
for three years.
Okay.
Hi. I'm Sandy.
And she's a little mannish.
( knocking on door )
( gasps )
Oh, my God! David!
Hi. I-Is this a bad time?
No, it's a great
time. Come in!
Wow! Hi!
Oh, my gosh!
What are you doing here?
Are you back from Minsk?
Well, just for
a couple of days.
I'm here to explain
to the people who gave
us our grant
why it's a positive thing
that we've spent all their money
and, uh... uh,
accomplished, uh, nothing.
Who cares?
It got you here!
Well, it got me
to New York, anyway
and then I got in a cab
at the airport
and the guy said, "Where to?"
and I just... gave him
your address.
I-I didn't even
think about it.
Wow. Where's your luggage.
Damn it.
All right. So I'll call
the cab company.
W-Wait. We can
call them later.
Can I just... you just
stand there for a moment?
( laughs nervously )
Boy. Y-You... There's an
old Russian expression.
Um, it goes...
Shtoa yazdeez vizshu: oi.
Um, roughly translated,
that means, um
"This thing I'm looking at:
wow."
Thank you.
God, no,
you should see me when...
Oh, actually, no,
I look pretty good.
Are... A-Are you kidding?
You know when you don't see
someone for a long time
and you kind of build
them up in your head
and then you start thinking,
"Come on, don't be crazy.
Nobody's that beautiful."
But... well, you are.
Ooh.
Well, so, uh...
well, are you seeing anyone?
No.
I'm just... I'm the
worst person ever!
How can I not tell David
that I'm seeing Mike?!
Maybe he didn't give you
a chance.
He said,
"Are you seeing someone?"
And I said, "No."
Oh, well, that would've been
your window.
Yeah. I mean
I don't know, I was looking...
I was looking in his eyes,
and I was just thinking
"Oh, my God, it's David.
David's here."
He's just,
he's so irresistible.
Really?
The scientist guy?
Really? Chandler?
Continue.
Okay, then it gets worse.
'Cause then I told him
that I would see him
tomorrow night.
Phoebe!
I know! Evil!
And-And-And...
I like Mike so much, you know.
It's just going really well.
Oh, my God!
Wow. Isn't it ironic
that David would show up
on the same day that
you and Mike exchange keys?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, you know, and given
my lifelong search for irony
you can imagine how happy I am.
What are you going to do?
I mean, I guess I just have
to... tell David
that nothing can happen
between us.
Unless I don't.
You know, complicated moral
situation-- no right, no wrong.
You have to tell David.
Okay, I knew
I should've had this
conversation with Joey.
Funniest guy she's ever met.
I'm funny, right?
What do you know?
You're a door.
You just like
"knock-knock" jokes.
Save it for inside.
Hey!
So, Oklahoma's a crazy place.
You know, they call it
the Sooner State.
Frankly, I'd sooner be
in any other state.
And what's with Oklahoma having
a panhandle?
Can all states have stuff
like that?
"Hey, yeah, I'm from the, uh,
waistband of Wyoming...
But when I was seven,
we headed over to the crotch."
Was your cabin pressurized?
( chuckles )
And don't get me started
on the way the people
from Tulsa talk.
Okay.
What's with the word "y'all"?
You know, just, two words
just pushed together?
Are we all allowed
to do that?
Because if so,
I say why stop there?
You know, your-your
"new poodle" could
be your "noodle."
And "fried chicken,"
could be "fricken."
Waiter! Waiter, excuse me.
"I'll have the fricken."
See, that's, that's funny
with the fricken, right?
No, it just reminded me
of something
this guy did today at work.
I-I told you about that
funny guy, Jeffrey, right?
Yeah, he came up.
Well, he did this bit...
You probably had to be there,
but it was, uh, Liza Minelli
locked in our freezer,
eating a raw chicken.
Oh!
( laughing )
Were you there?
No, but it sounds
like it was fricken funny.
I really do understand
how hard it's got to be
to leave your child
with another person.
I mean... it's like leaving
behind a piece of your heart.
Sandy, that's exactly
what it is.
Are you gay?
Ross!
It's okay. I get that a lot
doing what I do.
But I am straight.
I'm engaged, actually.
Her name's Delia.
Oh, that's pretty.
So you're-you're just...
like, a...
guy who's a nanny?
I realize how it's a bit
unorthodox for some people
but I really believe
the most satisfying thing
you can do with your life
is take care of a child.
Okay.
Like at my last job
I met Daniel
when he was three weeks old
and I got to watch him grow
into this awesome person.
When I left, I said,
"I'll see you soon"
and he said to me, "Skadandy..."
That was his name for me.
( laughs ):
Oh...
"I'll see you
every day, right in..."
( suppressed crying )
Oh...
Yeah, kids say
all kinds of crap.
( Emma crying )
Oh, God, she must need
her diaper changed.
Oh, oh, no, I
can take care of
that if you want.
Oh, that would be great.
Oh...
Okay.
I love him, I love
him, I love him.
Oh, come...
He's a guy.
So what? He's smart,
he's qualified.
Give me one good reason
we shouldn't try him out.
Because it's weird.
Why?
What kind of job is that
for a man? A nanny?
It's like if a woman
wanted to be...
Yes?
King?
I, uh, I hope you don't mind.
I used some
of my homemade lotion on Emma.
It's a mixture
of calendula and honey cream.
It'll dry that rash right up.
Plus, it keeps the hands young.
Yes! Sandy, you're hired!
That's great!
I'm sorry.
It's just such an
emotional thing
when you're welcomed
into a new family.
Oh, come on, come here.
You got to be at least bi.
Hey.
I need you to set me up
for a joke.
Later, when Monica's around
I need you to ask me
about fire trucks.
Ooh, I don't know, Chandler.
I'm not so good
with remembering lines.
Well, thank God your livelihood
doesn't depend on it.
I know, right?
Why-Why-Why are we doing this?
Monica says that
her maitre d'
is the funniest guy
she's ever met.
Seriously?
She actually said that?
Yes.
Am I crazy to be this upset?
No. Being funny's your thing.
Yeah.
Without that, you've just got
"lame with women."
Ye...
Hi.
There you are.
Fire trucks!
Wow, you-you look
even more beautiful
than you did yesterday.
Ooh.
In fact, um
I'm going to
kiss you now.
Oh, wait, wait.
Yeah, I can't get away
with stuff like that.
It-It sounded sexy
in my head, so I...
No, no, it's not that. Here.
Um, remember when you asked me
if I was seeing someone
and I said no?
Well, um, I am--
his name's Mike.
Oh.
Yeah.
I should have told you.
No.
Well, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No, it-it's okay.
I-I understand.
Mm-hmm.
Well, are you happy
with this guy?
I am happy.
Damn it.
I-I'm sorry.
I don't mean that.
I want you to be happy.
But only with me.
No. That's not fair.
Uh, who cares? Leave him.
I don't mean that.
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry. Um...
I-I think I... should
probably, uh, go.
Well...
But if, David, just...
I just want you to know
that-that, you know...
telling you this
is one of the hardest things
I've ever had to do.
Well, just so you know
hearing it wasn't exactly
a Vladnik carnival, either.
Can we at least
hug good-bye?
Of course, yeah.
You know, a kiss on the cheek
wouldn't be
totally inappropriate.
No, no.
I mean...
In Minsk...
Yeah?
it's, um, it's two
on each cheek...
Mm-hmm.
and, uh, and one
on the lips.
Well, if that's
what they do in Minsk...
In New York, it's...
( crying )
Oh, boy.
Hi.
Is everything all right?
Oh, yeah, it's
fine, it's fine.
Sandy was just...
was just telling me
about how he proposed
to his fiancée
and it was so beautiful.
Well, her favorite flower's
the camellia.
From the poem...
I can't... I can't
hear it again.
You know, I can't tell it again.
And I'm fine
never having heard it.
Rach, can I... can I
see you for a sec?
Yeah. Excuse me.
( Rachel sighs )
Do you realize
that man has cried in
our apartment three times.
Huh? I haven't cried that
many times since I moved in.
Oh, God.
Look, Ross, he's just...
Sandy's just sensitive,
that's all.
Okay, okay. See?
That is the problem.
He is too sensitive.
Too sensitive
to take care of our baby?
Yeah.
I mean, all I'm
saying is, that...
These are amazing.
Sandy made madeleines.
This-This is exactly
what I'm talking about.
What kind of a guy
makes-makes...
delicate French
cookies? Huh?
They're not even butch,
manly cookies with...
you know, with-
with-with chunks.
Well, you know,
I-I don't know what to say.
I mean, I never
thought of you
as a guy who needed
his men to be men.
You know? 'Cause I got
to tell you, Ross
it's not like you just came in
from branding cattle.
Hey, there's sensitive
and there's too sensitive.
Okay, what?
What is too sensitive?
( recorder playing
"Greensleeves" )
Mm, no, I can't.
I can't do this.
It's bad.
But it's nice.
And n... nice is good.
Mm-hmm.
And good is not bad.
Ergo... we should keep kissing.
No, no, no.
But...
ergo.
Look, David,
if you had never left
then, yeah, we'd probably
still be together right now
but... but you did leave,
and I'm-I'm with Mike
and I really care about him.
Um, good-bye. Uh...
Shtoa yazdeez vizshu: oi.
Well, hey, the key works.
You-- thanks for
the face massage.
Thank you.
Did Rachel tell you
we hired a male nanny?
Yeah.
I think that's great.
Oh, really?
Did she tell you
he plays the recorder
recites poetry
and bakes madeleines?
Oh. How are they?
Lighter than air,
but that's not the point.
Hey.
Rachel and I hired
a male nanny.
Really? Guys do that?
That's... weird.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's like a woman
wanting to be a...
A what? A what?
What's the end
of that sentence?
Yes. What is the end
Uh...
a penis model.
Look, anyway, hey,
did you tell Chandler
that some guy from work is
the funniest guy you ever met?
Yeah. So?
Wow.
Really? Do you
not know Chandler?
Is that why
he's acting so weird?
He's jealous?
My God, that is crazy.
It's not like
I'm attracted to Jeffrey.
So what?
Being funny is
Chandler's thing.
You know?
Like Ross's thing is...
Science?
Academia?
Being a good father?
No...
I can't believe
he's that upset about this.
Monica, you have to do some
damage control here, okay?
'Cause he's feeling...
Hey.
Hey, hey.
What are you guys
talking about?
Uh... Rachel and I, uh,
hired a male nanny.
You got a man who's a nanny?
You got a manny?
( hysterical laughter )
You know,
I don't mind a male nanny
but I do draw the line
at male wet nurse.
( gasping and guffawing )
Oh... oh...
you are on a roll, mister!
If I had known
you guys were coming over
I would have brought more pizza.
( hysterical laughter )
Okay! Okay! Stop it, you!
You stop it!
( gasping )
What is so funny
about that?
I don't know. It's...
Well, just the way you say it.
I mean, you're funny.
You got that funny thing.
You're a funny guy.
Did you tell her
what we talked about?
( laughing hysterically )
Yeah.
So those were pity laughs?
Pity laughs?!
Honey...
listen.
You have nothing to worry
about with Jeffrey.
Oh, yeah?
Is he funnier than me?
Well, you're-you're
different funny.
I mean, you're
more sarcastic
and-and... well, he does bits
and impressions and limericks.
I-I do limericks.
Uh, there once was
a man named Chandler
whose wife
made him die inside.
Honey, you know I think
you're hilarious.
Come on, you know that joke
you told me last week?
The one about Jerry Lewis and
the girl with the lazy eye.
Slayed me.
Hey...
I made up that joke
and told it to you.
Not knowing when to shut up.
Yep, that's my thing.
Yeah.
So...
how many guys have your key?
No, no, no, no.
It's not... it's not...
it's not as bad
as it looks, really.
I was just... I was saying
good-bye to an old friend.
Your lipstick's on his mouth.
Oh, uh... we just, uh,
happen to wear the same shade.
No, um... David and I
did used to go out.
But years ago,
and he lives in Minsk.
He's only... he's only in town
for a couple of days.
Did you, uh...
No, no.
Kiss him?
Oh, well, yeah.
Yes, but you should know
she really likes you.
In fact, I don't think
you realize
just how lucky you are, fella.
Don't point your finger at me.
Why? Wh-What are you going
to do about it?
Well... I'll
just show you
what I'm going
to do about it.
You want some
of that, huh?
Oh, really?
Well, shall we fight?
I can... okay.
Stop it! Stop it before
someone gets really hurt.
Here, David,
you should just go.
All right.
But... if I ever do
come back from Minsk
well, you'd just better
watch out.
Well, if I ever go to Minsk,
you'd better watch out.
Oh, you're going to Minsk?
Well, I might.
Really?
Well, if you do,
come in the spring.
It's just lovely there.
Okay, well, guys...
Well... good-bye, Phoebe.
Bye.
Hey, what, are
you kidding me?
Right-o, right-o.
Um...
Take good care of her.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
If you want your key back,
I totally understand.
It's never going to
happen again, right?
Right. Never, never, I swear.
Uh... oh, I just want to say,
if you, uh...
if you do ever come to Minsk,
that's my number.
Um... we'll, uh...
we'll party up Vladnik style.
( recorders playing
"Hot Cross Buns" )
Yeah, all right.
Hey, hey, Ross, check it out.
Sandy taught me
"Hot Cross Buns."
Really?
Sounded like "Three Blind Mice."
No, "Three Blind Mice"
goes like this.
I swear to God...
Who's up for puppets?
Me. I'm up for puppets.
Well, please welcome
the Snufflebumps.
Who wants to be Mr. Wigglemunch
and who's going to be
the Grumpus?
ROSS:
Okay, okay...
how exactly is a two-month-old
supposed to appreciate puppets?
Actually, studies have shown
that the movement and colors
help their cerebral development.
The whimsical characters
are just for us.
I want to be Mr. Wigglemunch.
Oh, my God.
Well, I guess we know
who's going to be the Grumpus.
( laughing )
Well, that was kind of rude.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please apologize to Sandy
and the Snufflebumps for me.
You know,
he was just doing his job.
You know what?
I'm... I'm sorry
I'm the only one
who isn't in love with
"Gary Poppins" out there...
But I-I-I just... I can't, I
can't go through with this.
Come on, Ross.
No. Hey, you
know what?
I'm sorry,
I would never force you
to hire someone you were
this uncomfortable with.
( sighs )
Oh, that's true.
Thank you.
Well, you're the one
who wants to fire him
so you're going to have
to go do it.
( chuckles )
So, you see, Wigglemunch
that's why
it's important to share.
I am learning so
much from you.
Well, I'm off to Tulsa
so if your maitre d' friend
has any funny Oklahoma jokes
tell him to e-mail me at
www.hahanotsomuch.com.
Honey, you can relax.
Last night at work, Jeffrey
told this really sexist joke.
After that,
not so funny anymore.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
See, that's the thing.
You got to keep
it smart, people.
Okay... don't miss that flight.
You know I love you.
I love you, too.
And I like you as a friend.
Right.
See you later.
See ya.
Did that guy
really make that joke?
No, he still kills me.
Last night he had me
laughing so hard
I swear a little pee came out.
Here it goes.
I can't watch.
It's like firing Elmo.
Sandy, hi.
Hi.
We, uh... we kind
of need to talk.
I'm afraid it's...
it's not working out.
Oh...
Yeah, um...
I mean, Rachel and I think
you are great with Emma.
Um... we just feel...
RACHEL:
You. You feel.
I...
just feel that the...
the chemistry isn't right.
I'm-I'm sorry.
We're... We're
more than happy
to give you a good
recommendation, and...
No, no, that's okay.
I've... had a lot of offers
from other families.
I... just picked you guys,
'cause I liked you the best.
RACHEL:
Oh, damn you, Geller.
Anyway, uh, well, I'm glad
there's no hard feelings.
No, none at all.
You need to be happy
with whoever's in your home.
Although, if you don't mind
telling me...
Hmm?
What was your problem?
Maybe it's something
I can work on in the future.
No... you know, it's-it's,
uh, nothing you did.
It's... it's, uh...
it's my issue.
What is it?
( chuckles uncomfortably )
Please?
You know, I'm just not, um...
that comfortable with a guy
who's as sensitive as you.
( sighs )
That's fair.
Although, can I ask...
why do you think that is?
Why? I-I don't know.
Um... uh...
maybe... maybe because
of my father?
Mmm.
I mean, um, you know,
when I was growing up
he was kind of a tough guy.
And as a kid I wasn't
the athlete I am now.
( Rachel guffaws )
I play squash!
Anyway... I, um...
I always got the feeling he
thought I was too sensitive.
That must have been hard.
It was hard.
No, I remember I
was in my bedroom
playing with my dinosaurs--
playing and learning--
and my father walks
in and he says...
he says, "What are you
doing with those things?
"What's wrong with you?
"Why aren't you...
Why aren't you outside playing
like a... like a real boy?"
But you are a real boy.
( crying ):
I know I am.
And when it's summer
and it's hot
why can't you wear a tank top?
It's all right.
Crying is good.
It lets the boo-hoos out.
Here comes some more.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
And what's the
one kind of boat
that can never ever sink?
What kind?
A friendship.
Wow, you blow my mind.
Oh, I got to go.
Oh... how much
do I owe you?
20 bucks.
Oh, it's like
the cheapest college ever.